Okay, very good on this, my name
is Dev, in today's video we are going to talk
about the advantages and disadvantages of health insurance, so guys, first of all this is
not a sponsored video, it's a normal one, as many
videos you will see are from the real sponsors, so by
drinking my juice, I will
go into the complete details of the policy, this is a good wedding policy, because the health
insurance statement is a very big
comment, why talk about leaders in this book, it is
star health insurance,
this is such yoga, or there are many such
players here and I have already experienced three-four
shortcomings, so
I know very well how to click on health issues here,
what important things should be seen
when you have to buy a policy, that is
health insurance, so I have
downloaded their entire prospectus from Navi's website here, I have read it properly, but
you can also explore the ointment app,
I have also considered the premium here and compared it  So
after knowing everything, we are going to
talk about its advantages and disadvantages,
we will talk about all that. So
first of all, the
unwanted liver probe into 10 minutes,
see, the sailor cleans itself, I did
not find any such verified data, I got it on Ashwin's
return that
according to the alarm set in the details, the
clean is approved within 10 minutes,
if you complain about it along with the
complaint, then
in the TP section of the hospital, where you give the
application for cashless treatment or
you can send me the claim number, then
normally if there is constipation, then
a computer does it for 30 minutes minimum and
whatever you get cleaned within half an hour,
if it is cashless treatment, then instantly
here the 30-minute camera claim is
also approved, okay, for
this reason, I found out that their pre-
hospitalization is behind the jewellery TDS, whereas whatever
deficiency there is,  It normally provides you 60s
like star help or it is
done, so if the expenses before going to the hospital,
well, the expenses before getting admitted in the hospital, then
you will get nighty dress here,
at the beginning of the base reduction, you will get it for 160,
apart from this, the third
advantage I got is for the post production, but
this product Tanwar has provided you TDS,
whereas if there is any deficiency, we
provide it to Noida, that is, after you are discharged,
whatever medicines you have expressed at home, if
any of them are
express, then 180 will be
covered by it, but if along with deficiency,
I provide you the same 90s, that
gas switch advantage, that
your consumers who were also here, are also here, whoever got
gas, went to Moscow, got
head charges, so normally if it does
not reduce, when the insurance is made, which
explains the adventures, then its
amount is between 500 to 1000.
You have to pay the hospital for all these
things. Health insurance does
not provide you, but right now the skin from turmeric
which is given to non-customers is mostly
limited here. Apart from that, the next benefit
I got is the maternity cover which is
provided here, which normal other insurance companies do
not provide right now, and even if they do, then the
incident happens under the same conditions. First
thing is this third benefit is for premature delivery
within the entire life of one plus the
waiting period here is 36
years, which means if you are taking the policy today, then
after three years if your wife gets
pregnant then you get cover here.
Along with this, additional fees are
also charged here, so if you make a policy on novel rupees, then
I think around 100 rupees, then there is no
extra fee.
Within 3 years, you can say that there will be
more expenditure on 36 bed sheets here.
Your friend Mukesh does not have maximum coverage,
he also provides maternity cover
but you have to follow some terms and conditions.
Firstly, the normal life of those cigarettes is
two years instead of three years and the second thing which is the
best is like for a particular one,
if the time is wide then only it will provide it, it does
not provide it to those with Rs. 500003,
apart from this, the other benefits which I
click here, like health checkups,
bonuses are provided, if you do
not clear then there is unlimited online
consultation, all these things are provided by most of your
companies here, so
if you cannot also make a different shade,
now let's talk about the
disadvantages of Naveen
Health Insurance, then the first thing
I have seen is that the
cashless hospitals are
shown on their website, but when I
call inside the hospital, their team definitely visits and
asks them whether they have got
rid of the help with you or not, then
they clearly refuse here, so guys,
here you will have to go first of all,
I will trust anyone first because
my first night is that my
The treatment is through cashless hospitals
and the cashless hospitals are located as close to my house as possible.
So the
first thing you should know is whether the
hospital listed on their website has a
tube or not, is the
actual treatment possible there
or not. The setting is such that I can get
any other variant of the policy for Brigadier Nabhi, which is provided by Star
Health. I get a lot of benefits.
If I take a super policy, I can get
individual coverage in the center, then
after that, family coverage. I get this thing,
but the individual variants are
also available to me well. So, the
disadvantage here is that I have to go through the
entire process on the app. There is
no entry fee for the website, nor is there any clean process. There is no
login system on the website. So,
this thing seemed a bit odd to me and secondly,
I recently saw that the
health insurance app provided by Nabhi has been removed from here
and it has been inserted.  It was also launched, the
meaning is the same, you have included loan,
health tips and
investment, it has been forcibly delayed, it
seems that there is a disadvantage in it that
Navik is not a dedicated health service provider,
if I talk about top companies
like Star Health Insurance and
Care, then both of them are dedicated only
in the health and wealth segment,
but it is like many other companies,
like people have invested in it, it has been invested
and it has also launched home loan in the list, so it
means a whole
huge segment is gaining momentum here
and it is a new company, so I think it should have
dedication here also on one front,
I have got disadvantages of it that all the
aggregators like
Policy Bazaar, Insurance,
it is not linked with any Heroin,
nor is their policy
shown by comparing it with the company's policy, then if you look at
Policy Bazaar, you can compare the
policies of all the leading brands with normal ones.  You
can choose easily but right now there is
no type anywhere, till now this last not
deleted or the navel company which Sachin Bansal has basically
formed is an investment company,
definitely the whole tabs are question
tags too, Tanu has invested in it even today, I will take all this
but what you
see here is if the profits of clean are increasing
like you must have seen that Star Health
Insurance recently launched its IPO, so if
you see their profits, the profits of the company were
quite good in the beginning but as it is quoted then
Gurjar 20 21 centers got ruined, these guys
I have told you the advantages and disadvantages on family basis,
so
by using all these you can choose a good
health insurance service provider company for yourself, so
guys that Light this
Video plz subscribe Channel do
not forget to join the Telegram channel,
thank you, thank you